Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Oh, oh, oh, oh
Mock? That's right.
He's my hero.
He's always laughing and
dancing to a rhythm like this.
Kuma's Life.
Hey, Bonnie, Bonnie, Bonnie!
Come on.
Not just Bonnie, Captain Bonnie.
Ha, Captain, take it easy.
This is the one.
Kumachi is on that island.
What? Are you sure?
As sure as I can be!
Problem is, the place is
swarming with marines right now.
Dad...
Mainland Vulcan!
Time to go!
Look out!
It's the body pirates!
HQ said that they're a priority target!
Everywhere they go, they leave
injured children and senior citizens!
Bastards!
They're too scared to pick on
someone who can fight back!
Let's make these dirtbags pay! Fire!
Out of my way!
It's yours!
Kumaji!
Come on in, it's us!
A big guy wearing black.
I think I just saw him
on the edge of town.
Captain!
There's been a Kumaji satin!
Be right there!
Which way?
At the edge of town! Got it!
I wish I could explain, Bonnie.
But we can't see each other.
Please stop looking for me.
Why wasn't he there?
Don't rush it.
Pirates like us have all
the time in the world.
That's right.
Nika.
I want to look for Nika, too!
Then, when I do find Dad, I
can tell him I met his hero.
He'll be so excited.
Meanwhile, in the east blue...
Gum-Gum!
The upstart pirate Straw Hat
Luffy suddenly rose to prominence.
after taking down Arlong and his crew.
All right!
I got a real bounty!
I'm headed out to Log Town.
What for?
Want me to come along?
It's fine.
But for the record,
who is in charge there?
Should be Captain Smoker.
Jinbei, look!
Can you guess how I know this pirate here?
Luffy is my little brother!
Wait, he's what?
The kid who beat the Arlong
Pirates is your brother?
Funny how things work out, huh, Dragon?
Both of our children became pirates.
This is the iron code that
all pirates must live by.
Plunder all treasure in sight!
Plunder treasure!
Only from bad guys!
Never show mercy!
No mercy!
But be nice!
Is this right?
You nailed it!
I mean, I'm not an expert,
but it looks good to me.
Yes, I'm mature.
I put some jewelry on my cheeks so
Dad can recognize me without my gems.
Now all that's left is to get famous!
That way he'll be able
to find me for sure!
He'll find me. Right, Dad?
Very unsettling.
I'm sure it is.
But these clones and your modifications
are going to change the world.
And speaking of itch,
did you hear about the pirate who
declared war on the government?
Shoot down that flag. Roger.
Huh?
The boy is Dragon Son, you say?
You'll see my memories eventually, so
there's no point in hiding it from you.
What caught my attention is that Straw Hat
fights for freedom with
the power of rubber.
He sounds a lot like my hero. Nika.
He does indeed.
Here we go!
The Bomb Giant Jet Show!
My orders are to annihilate
every last one of you without
exception but i will spare your
lives in exchange for the head of
Straw Hat luffy the government
should be satisfied with his life
alone you want us to betray our
captain not a chance what a pity
you want someone's head
fine i'll give you one but
i can't let you have my
captains So take mine instead
Because Luffy is the man
who will become king of
the pirates If you truly
wish to take his place
You must be willing to
accept his agony yourself
This would be enough
to knock me unconscious
He inspires such loyalty in his friends
He couldn't be anyone's
son but yours, dragon
Seven warlords, report in immediately.
Refuse and lose your title.
That's awfully dramatic.
What happened?
Preparations for the
execution of Porcus D.
Ace.
He's a standard bearer
to the new generation.
But he's a son to Whitebeard.
We expect war.
A war with the Whitebeard pirates?
Don't worry, I'll be there.
Where's the rest of the food?
Bring it before I starve! Pizza!
I'll get more pizza!
Captain, I swear they're cooking as
fast as I can! Really? Of course!
Please don't make a scene, Captain!
This will be the last
time I see you, Bonnie.
You've become quite the
pirate, haven't you?
A pirate punched a celestial dragon!
Human shot.
Can someone attack a celestial dragon?
The whole world knows that's forbidden.
And to do it so close to
Navy HQ, this is suicide!
It's them.
The Straw Hat Pirates.
Are they trying to protect
a fish man and a mermaid?
What have you done, Straw Hat Luffy?
This is an unimaginable act of rebellion.
No one has even attempted such a thing.
Not for centuries.
Stand down, Pucci.
Dragon... Eva...
Forgive me for disappearing
without a word.
I leave only two things behind as
proof that I existed in this world.
Lonnie, and the future of
this boy, Straw Hat Luffy.
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
Nothing, but this is how
harsh the new world will be.
You and your friends aren't ready
for it You must grow stronger
And when the time comes
Someday You'll save this world
A self-destruct switch Do you
really fear Kuma that much?
You did turn him into a deadly
human weapon Did you not?
You're at the top of his authority ladder.
And if he goes berserk when we're out of
command range, who will stop him and how?
I don't!
Cease your insolence,
you paltry hired hand.
All right, I'll do as you ask, but
please let him keep some free will.
I've invented a brain circuit that
can toggle between personality modes.
It will be easy to install,
I promise you just...
I gave you a very clear order, Vegapunk.
Destroy every trace of his free will.
We're both men of science.
You can't fool me.
But what will become of his daughter?
What of Bonnie?
He will never see her again!
Thank you for trying, Vigipunk.
You didn't hear all of that, did you?
Turns out a scientist gave
me superhuman hearing.
All right, today's the day
you lose your free will.
I've only known you for two years,
but we've had some good times.
We have.
Seems your first mission will be a large-scale
fight against the Whitebeard pilots.
The Navy's requesting a
massive deployment of clones.
If you wouldn't mind, could you
program one more mission after that?
You want to guard the Strawhead's ship?
Until one of his crewmates comes back.
I want to help them protect their home.
It's a shame.
I wish that I could watch
their journey to the end?
What is it that you expect from that boy?
His actions move my soul.
I don't know how else to put it.
He's a legend come to life.
I know Nika is just an old folk tale.
But I told Bonnie that there's a warrior
who moves to the rhythm of liberation.
and brings smiles to all.
If there really is a hero who
can change the world like Nika?
I think it'll be Straw Hat.
A revolutionary betting on a pirate?
You've chosen quite the dark horse.
What a contradiction.
Proof you're still human.
Now, about that sample for my research.
We had a deal, right?
Then you push your memories
into a paw like that.
Do you forget them?
No, it's like a copy, but it will
vanish after someone touches it.
Fine with me.
I devised a method to study it remotely.
Keep it right there.
Now, let's get this over with.
Purely clinical, I am a scientist.
I see.
So this is my life.
I wonder how many people I've
troubled through the years.
Troubled, you say?
Why, to live is to trouble others.
By the way, what age
did you become a slave?
When I was four.
Same as me!
Kumachi!
I'm the eldest here by four years, so
that means it's my job to keep you fed!
Kumaji!
That's enough!
Let's sell them!
Kumaji! Kumaji!
Kumachi!
I'm full!
I'm so happy!
Kumachi...
I'll always, always, love you.
Don't worry, Jenny.
I'll raise your daughter as my home.
Daddy!
Dad?
Those little jerks!
They were making fun
of my face rocks again.
I wish I could throw them at them.
Guess they are kind of ugly.
But I'm stuck with them.
They're permanent.
I'm going to be honest with you.
Your daughter has five
years to live at most.
She would be beating the odds just
to make it to her 10th birthday.
I'm afraid your mother's dead.
But that means she's in heaven now.
You'll be okay, Kuma.
You're strong.
You just have to survive.
Don't give up. Why?
I think I'd be better off dead, too.
The warrior of liberation will
save you. Have faith. He'll come.
Who is that?
I can't take it anymore.
I'd rather die!
I can't lose anyone else!
I won't lose anyone else!
Mock?
That's right.
He's my hero.
Does that mean he'll come and free me too?
A mass of pain and suffering
won't just go away.
In the end, someone has to accept it.
Never forget, those hands
can do more than pray.
They're the hands of liberation!
Thank you.
If you can help Bonnie get well,
then I'll happily accept any fate.
Any fate at all.
Nika, the Sun God.
He'll show up and deliver
us all to freedom one day.
He'll take you to the sea,
beneath the free skies.
Are you sure? Of course.
He's no joke.
My disease will be all gone in a year.
Then I can finally go outside!
When I pick you up, we'll take to the sea.
From there, it's an endless
horizon. Can't wait!
I want to go all kinds of places!
Bonnie.
Ever since I was young, I've had a dream.
I've always wanted to be a hero.
Someone who could save the downtrodden
and free people from suffering.
Kuma!
Kuma-chi!
Kuma.
Kuma!
Kuma-chi!
I'll cure her!
Daddy, you're home!
I'm so glad.
Thank you.
Yes, to live is to trouble others.
Your death will trouble
everyone who loves you.
It's proof of a life they lived.
I tell you, Kuma, you are a hero.
You're Bonnie's hero.
You're everyone's hero.
You're too kind, Vang.
Vegapunk.
I know.
I will.
Mock?
That's right.
He's my hero.
Does that mean he'll
come and free me, too?
Of course you will.
Thank you, Vegapunk, for saving Bonnie.
Could you pass on a message for me?
The next time you see her!
Tell her!
Happy 10th birthday.
Oh, I'll be home to me.
I should go to my house.
No one cannot be my hair.
The voice of my voice is me.
How long should I take my hand?
I can't see the next one.
Then move me.